<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>The Avail Programming Language</title>
		<description>Fresh posts on the site, including newsletters, tutorials, documentation, etc.</description>
		<link>http://www.availlang.org</link>
		<item>
			<title>Privacy Policy Update</title>
			<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 03:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<description> We have enabled Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting in the hope that it will provide information helpful in expanding our audience, and have updated our Privacy Policy accordingly.</description>
			<link>http://www.availlang.org/about-us/policies/privacy-policy.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.availlang.org/about-us/policies/privacy-policy.html</guid>
  		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Team and tutorial updates</title>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 04:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<description> The Avail team welcomes its newest members, Evan Beach and Peter Monks. There have also been minor fixes to the tutorials.</description>
			<link>http://www.availlang.org/about-us/team/index.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.availlang.org/about-us/team/index.html</guid>
  		</item>
		<item>
			<title>FAQ</title>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 05:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>The Avail FAQ is now available.</description>
			<link>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/documentation/faq.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/documentation/faq.html</guid>
  		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Newsletter #6 - Hello, World!</title>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>Today is release day, and the Avail programming language is now live. The first released version of Avail is "1.0.0 DEV 2014-04-28". This is the first major development milestone. It is not a production release, and is not recommended for mission-critical use.</description>
			<link>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/newsletters/E006.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/newsletters/E006.html</guid>
  		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Newsletter #5 - The Builder</title>
			<pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2014 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>It's been a busy few months, but now it's time to showcase the recent rework of Avail's most-used tool: The Builder. We need to put on our best (inter)face as we approach our release date and prepare to greet the world…</description>
			<link>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/newsletters/E005.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/newsletters/E005.html</guid>
  		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Newsletter #4 - Victim of Success</title>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>I thought about calling this newsletter "So-so Things Come To Those Who Wait for a Few Days", but figured that the necrohippoflagellation had to stop somewhere. Since the release of the new website, there has been a dramatic upswing in site visits and new visitors. Hello, world! Thank you for visiting our humble site! Unfortunately our site is just that, humble, even though the Avail team isn't terribly humble about what it's doing. Speaking of all-encompassing greetings…</description>
			<link>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/newsletters/E004.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/newsletters/E004.html</guid>
  		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tutorial - Reverse Polish Notation</title>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>Discover how to build a Reverse Polish notation expression language without writing a parser, expression nodes, operand stack, or interpreter. This is a great computer science classic, except for the part where you're done coding it in three minutes.</description>
			<link>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/learn/tutorials/hello-world.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/learn/tutorials/hello-world.html</guid>
  		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tutorial - Hello world!</title>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>Inspired by the many such programs that have been written since the 1967 BCPL progenitor, this archetypal and obligatory introduction demonstrates how a bright-eyed programmer can greet the entire world with just a few lines of code. (N.B.: This does not actually greet the entire world, which would be quite spooky and odd. Do not fear.)</description>
			<link>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/learn/tutorials/rpn.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.availlang.org/about-avail/learn/tutorials/rpn.html</guid>
  		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>